https://www.cherokee.org/privacy-policy/

Privacy Policy
The Cherokee Nation maintains this server to enhance public access to Cherokee Nation information. Cherokee Nation provides no warranty, expressed or implied, as to the accuracy, reliability or completeness of furnished data.Only public information will be maintained on the Cherokee Nation home page or made accessible through links to other web pages. We strongly recommend that Cherokee Nation data be acquired directly from a Cherokee Nation server and not through other sources that may change the data in some way. Use external links only when there is a direct relationship between the program coverage of the Cherokee Nation home page and the material to which it links.This site contains live references (or pointers) to information created and maintained by other organizations including plug-in downloads used to view various content on the Cherokee Nation web site. Please note that Cherokee Nation does not control, endorse, and cannot guarantee the relevance, timeliness, or accuracy of these outside materials or plug-in downloads. We cannot guarantee the safety of your personal computer from visiting or downloading from sites outside of cherokee.org.While Cherokee Nation makes every effort to provide accurate and complete information, various data such as names, telephone numbers, etc. may change prior to updating. Cherokee Nation welcomes suggestions on how to improve our home page and correct errors.
communications@cherokee.org
Policy on the use of content or media provided on cherokee.orgMedia found on the cherokee.org and affiliated web sites may be used on individual web sites or published documents as long as the following General guidelines are met:You may not use the Cherokee Nation images, media, or content and claim it as your own.If the seal is used, the image should be a direct link to www.cherokee.org.You may not claim to represent the Cherokee Nation or act as a representative, in any way, of theCherokee Nation.Content used must reference www.cherokee.org as the source.You may not use the Cherokee Nation, web site images, media, or content defamatory way.The page and web site must not advocate illegal actions, contain pornography, or belong to, or encourage, racial hate groups.The page cannot advocate the non-recognition of the government of any federally recognized Indian Nation.The page or web site must not present a conflict of interest with existing Cherokee Nation policies.
Disclaimer regarding cultural information:
Cultural information provided in the Cherokee Link newsletter or this web site may vary from clan to clan, location to location, family to family, and from differing opinions and experiences. Information provided is not 'etched in stone'.Disclaimer regarding events:These events are not Cherokee Nation related unless otherwise specified. The events are not guaranteed of relevance of information by the Cherokee Nation. For any information regarding an individuals event, you are recommended to contact them directly.Disclaimer regarding links:These links are maintained outside of the Cherokee Nation web server and are not guaranteed of the relevance of information or downtime resulting from other servers. For any information regarding an individuals web site, you are recommended to contact them directly.Privacy Statement:At Cherokee Nation, we are committed to protecting your privacy. You can travel through most of our site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services or gather statistics. This privacy statement explains data collection and use practices of Cherokee.org; it does not apply to other Cherokee Nation Affiliated sites, products or services.Collecting your Personal InformationWe will ask you when we need information that personally identifies you (personal information) or allows us to contact you. Generally, this information is requested when you are entering a contest, subscribing to e-mail newsletters, signing up for an event or service, or filling out online survey's or polls. Personal information collected by Cherokee.org often is limited to e-mail address and name but may include other information when needed to provide a service you requested.Privacy InformationCherokee Nation does not share or sell any personal information collected with any other internal or any external entities. Personally identifying information you provide will be used only in connection with Cherokee Nation programs and services in which you supply information for or for such other purposes as are described at the point of collection.Children and PrivacyOur websites do not target and are not intended to attract children under the age of 13. Cherokee Nation does not knowingly solicit personal information from children under the age of 13 or send them requests for personal information.Cookies and Tracking TechnologyA cookie is a small data file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as a user ID that the site uses to track the pages you've visited, but the only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply yourself. A cookie can't read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Some parts of the Cherokee Nation's web site uses cookies to track user traffic patterns. We do this in order to determine the usefulness of our website information to our users and to see how effective our navigational structure is in helping users reach that information.If you prefer not to receive cookies while browsing our website, you can set your browser to warn you before accepting cookies and refuse the cookie when your browser alerts you to its presence. You can also refuse all cookies by turning them off in your browser, although you may not be able to take full advantage of Cherokee Nation's web site if you do so. You do not need to have cookies turned on to use/navigate through many parts of our web site, except access to certain of Cherokee Nation's web pages require a login and password.Changes to this Privacy PolicyCherokee Nation will amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site.Disclaimer regarding Independent Press Act of 2000When the Cherokee Independent Press Act of 2000 (Legislative Act 11-00) was approved by the Tribal Council and signed into law by Principal Chief Chad Smith in July 2000, Section 10 of that act superseded previous legislation requiring the publication of the council meeting minutes and the travel expenses of elected officials on the Cherokee Nation Web site and quarterly notification of Cherokee Phoenix readers that the information was posted on the Web site.Questions or SuggestionsIf you have questions or concerns about our collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, please email us at communications@cherokee.org.
Copyright © 2020 Cherokee Nation. All rights reserved.
Last Updated:6/2/2020
Privacy Policy
